## **Software Developer**

# **WILSON WU**

**U** 0123 456789

johndoe.com

n johnyD

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Company A**

**Developer |** since January 2016

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

#### **Company B**

Frontend Developer | January 2015 - December 2015

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

## **Company C**

Trainee | March 2014 - December 2014

Making coffee and baking cookies.

## **EDUCATION**

Major in Hacking and Computer Penetration, University A, New York, USA.

Master of Arts | March 2012 - December 2013

Major in Engineering, University B, Los Angeles, USA.

Bachelor of Science | March 2009 - December 2011

## **SKILLS**

Also proficient in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, grew up bilingual (English and Klingon).

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Angular 2
- TypeScript
- ES.Next
- Docker

## **About me**

I am currently working as a Senior Developer Level 2/Tech Lead in the Gaming Industry. I gained my master's degree in computer science in 2007. Worked as full stack developer from 2007 to 2009 by building intelligent building management systems with C++ and SQL. In 2009, I joined the gaming industry, became a front-end developer working on C++, ActionScript, JavaScript, and typescript. I created my first